[{"answer": "", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah, they flip a coin", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "my friend, bumpe", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Could be years before I get back to that place. I can't go to rides alone", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Me? No, no, I don't, I don't. Doing very well, very well, yep", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah I'm, eh, in 'the market'", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "So, you're in 'the market'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Which market", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "She? She works, he doesn't. He sounds like my son", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "There is no he. So, who's getting married", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "There is no he. So, who's getting married", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Lesbian wedding", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well, this is where I get off", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Eh, hey why don't you...oh nothing", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "But it rained last night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "His mudda' was a mudda'", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "You oughta' sit here. There is a difference", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I got something against yours. How about a couple of deep knee bends, maybe a squat thrust", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You got something against naked body", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Who's got time for squat thrusts", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "All right, how about skipping breakfast. I'm guessing you're not a 'hal", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I understand, I like good breakfast. Long as you don't wind up trapped in a room with bimbo broals and pigtails, been counseled by my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Really? But, it's a little bit slow out there it rained last night", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "His father was a mudda'", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Oh, this baby loves the slob, loves it, eats it up. Eats the slob. Born in the slob. His father was a mudda'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "His mother was a mudda'", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "His father was a mudda'", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "His mother was a mudda'", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "They still have no pitching. my friend's a question mahk. ...You don't recover from those rotator cuffs so fast", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "No hitting? They got hitting! my friend, my friend. ...They got no defence", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Defence? Please. ...They need speed", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "my friend's no good? ...They got no team leaders", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Speed? They got my friend. ...They need a bullpen", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "They got Franco! ...What they need is a front office", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "my friend's no good? ...They got no team leaders", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "But you gotta like their chances", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "What's going on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Subway.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Get going? But we haven't really, you know...", "qsentId": 38}]